All right. That looks sick. All right. Now I really want you to like spend some time
going through this so rare application. Again, remember that I like to focus on playing
in the limited series championship matches, specifically the by weekly ones I believe.
So I usually play what say two to three teams and I'm going to have you set those teams
going forward. So if you can kind of just display to me, what you think the key information
is that I can consume it to understand, you know, when matches are ending, when new matches
are starting and what the scores are and what place I'm in for the matches that are getting close
to ending, that would be fantastic. So give that a shot. Let's see what you can do. Again, spend some
time like really thinking hard about what this should look like. I really wanted to be like a
premium part of this dashboard. Thanks.