All right. I think that's starting to look pretty good. Now double check the so
rare MBA widget because you missed a lot. You're saying only have one card
right now where I have many more. I know I have at least three line ups that you
should remember roughly setting them. So just double triple quadruple check
my so rare data and I only want you to build me a so rare widget if you
actually think you can build me one that is good enough and can update on
a regular basis and can basically make it so that I don't have to go into the
so rare website and I can just tell you what I want you to do and I can just use
this widget as basically my so widget for information that I need about
so rare including wallet balance and all that type of stuff. Thanks.